### Jullian Anthony Sy-Lucero

228 Mississauga Valley Blvd Mississauga, Ontario L5A 1Y8

+1 (647) 838-3862 | jsylucero@outlook.com

Career Objectives	To gain knowledge and experience in the field of Information Technology, as part of a team and individual while working within a respectful and diversified work environment.
Skills	<ul> <li>General knowledge of Microsoft Windows, Apple macOS, and Linux Distros</li> <li>Knowledge of Microsoft Office such as Word, Excel, and Power Point</li> <li>Knowledge of IDEs such as Visual Studio, Eclipse, WebStorm and PHPStorm.</li> <li>Knowledge of coding languages such as Microsoft Visual C# in Visual Studio, Java, JavaScript and PHP</li> <li>Knowledge of Frameworks such as ReactJS, and Angular</li> <li>Experience working with NodeJS runtime and package manager</li> <li>Knowledge of SQL Databases.</li> <li>Knowledge of Git repositories.</li> <li>Knowledge of Microsoft Visual C# in Microsoft Visual Studio</li> <li>Extensive knowledge of Website Development (MEAN, and MERN stacks)</li> <li>Extensive knowledge of designing using Photoshop.</li> <li>Experience with continuous integration, problem-solving, and creative thinking</li> </ul>
Work Experience	
June 2017 – July 2017 Toronto, ON	<ul> <li>Web Designer &amp; Developer / Receptionist</li> <li>Parkdale Golden Age Foundation</li> <li>Updated website information</li> <li>Improved and added to the company's website designs     Added CSS stylings in order to adjust already existing elements to     improve and adjust positions.</li> <li>Updated PGAF's Mailable Donation Form to fit a more current     design.</li> <li>Created a newly designed brochure for the company</li> </ul>

# September 2017 - April 2018 Toronto, ON

WordPress and React Developer | Elephant Space

- Developed and setup REST API Routes for use within the WordPress and React environments
- Adjusted several designs to Elephant Space's website in order to improve visual appeal and feel
- Developed as part of a team to create a not-yet-released React Application within the WordPress site
- Coordinated the main designs of Elephant Space's React Application
- Developed the basic/template layouts of Elephant Space's React Application components to be as modular as possible for ease of development for the team.
- Co-developed a donation system which would allow users to login to Facebook to display their names and donation amount or to remain anonymous on the donation wall.
- Developed the design of the donation wall, as well as improved the layout of Elephant Space's Donation page
- Participated in several developments that aimed to improve the team's development cycle within the back-end.

## June 2018 - July 2018 Toronto, ON

Web Designer & Developer / Receptionist Parkdale Golden Age Foundation

- Created a site dashboard to add more functionality and ease-ofmanagement to the organisation's site.
- Created an upload API back-end, using PHP as the development language
- Created an email API back-end for their front-end page contact forms as the default provided email system gave out a spam-like email, using PHP as the development language
- Updated contact form designs on the front-end
- Created a paper form for organisation memberships
- Improved upon the previous year's website design and layout to assure that designs are more superfluous and seamless

#### **Other Activities**

#### George Brown College T127 - COMP1230

Team/Group Assignment

 Guided team as a leader to successfully complete the given assignment to create a PHP website.

Education and Professional Development	
September 2011 - June 2015 Mississauga, ON	Father Michael Goetz Catholic Secondary School High School Diploma Student
September 2015 - Present Toronto, ON	George Brown College of Arts, Design and Information Technology Advanced Ontario College Diploma, Computer Programmer Analyst (T127)
Languages	<ul><li>English</li><li>Filipino (Tagalog)</li></ul>